Holy crap!
Are you kidding me?
Oniwa Banshu are down!
The Mimawari Kuma are toast!
We got no one left!
Daikoku!
Kazukage!
Captain Head!
I knew he had a reputation,
but I wasn't expecting this.
He didn't just resist the virus.
He used its power to wreck our troops.
I see why the land of Juana has
remained untouched for so many years.
It's an island of monsters.
Vos, no!
Is this the only way?
What are you waiting for, Yadda-Bee?
Empty your mind and calm yourself.
You know what'll happen
if I become an Oni.
I'm sorry.
Please give me a second to compose myself.
I'll do it soon.
I'll do it now!
I do not envy you.
Of course it's hard.
He is like a father to us.
I'm losing control, Sangoro! Do it!
You won't go alone, boss!
I shall be with you soon!
Come on, please!
Can't you help them, Mr.
Raccoon?
There's no time!
There's no saving me anymore!
You don't have to be afraid!
Now cut me down!
I don't want to hurt you!
If you don't do it, I won't
be able to control myself.
We have done our best, but this is it.
Mr Raccoon, if we don't get that cure now,
this whole floor, all of our friends
will become ice! It's Oni again.
Help us, Master Queen!
Master Queen!
All of your men have
served you faithfully.
Why do we have to die from
your virus alongside the enemy?
Buzz off!
Why should I lift a finger for you?
You peons aren't worth saving!
You ever consider that?
Listen, morons.
If I don't have any use for you,
you're no better than garbage.
Show some respect.
That virus is my masterpiece.
In fact, it was created to
erase your deficiencies.
You hear that, Pleasures?
You already lost the Devil Fruit Lottery,
so it's not like you're gonna
ever amount to anything.
You're nothing but giggling cannon fodder.
Ha ha, ha, ha, cruel!
As for you waiters, no matter how long
you wait, no more smile fruits are coming.
You lost your chance.
You'd know better than the pleasures.
The eternal waiters.
A living tragedy, a colossal
monument to failure.
The only way you scrubs can help the beast
pirates is to become an
oni and cause some chaos!
before you kick the bucket! Ya dig?
It's better to burn out than fade away.
Wait, this is like
you're telling us to die?
And why not?
We have more than enough troops.
How could you say that?
You're sick!
I gave you a chance!
That antibody could save
a couple of you at least!
Damn it.
I'm not going to die like this.
Cut down the samurai.
Cut down the oni.
Every man for himself.
Now you're motivated.
Some of you might even survive.
This guy is a monster.
I can't believe they follow him.
Well, that's pirates for you.
Listen up, you damned samurai.
You might want to think about
what you're protecting right now.
Now, that raccoon made some big
promises, but he's a pirate just like us.
Don't you dare.
You really think he can mass-produce
antibodies that quickly?
He tricked you!
He was infected as well.
He probably took the antibody
for himself and got the hell out.
The Straw Hats are nothing like you!
How can you be so sure?
You think pirates have morals?
This may be farewell for now, but
I'll follow you sooner or later boss.
Don't be so hasty to follow!
Farewell.
Don't do it!
What the hell?
Please, Mr.
Raccoon, don't try and stop me.
We're losing him.
This was his choice.
I'm going to save him!
Stand back and watch!
This will work!
Swallow it, boss!
That was close!
You guys scared me!
So, did that fix him?
All right!
It's working fine! See?
His body's warming up!
Oh, you're not dead, are you?
Tell me you're alive, boss.
I am.
Yes, I knew you could
do it, Mr. Raccoon Dog.
The boss is okay.
Yuck! Tristan!
You'd better hurry!
We're on it, Dr. Chopper!
Is that a cannon?
Okay, it's ready.
Just give the word.
Oh, let me get attacked!
Dr.
Chopper, do the honors!
Wait, what?
My Shuffer-Fade Snap-Do-Lyzer!
Fire! Fire!
Happy one!
Inhale the mist!
What the hell do you think
you're doing, you damn raccoon?
You've destroyed my masterpiece!
How did you even pull that off?
Even with the cure,
it's impossible to give
the medicine to everyone on
the floor since you made sure
to infect so many people.
So I crafted a virus out of the
antibody, one that spreads just as fast.
You what?
If you can make a bad virus, I
can beat it with a good virus.
I had to get creative and
distribute it through mist.
But all they need to do is breathe it in!
You're just a doctor from
a ratty little pirate crew!
How the hell did you
learn a trick like that?
Because our crew has traveled the
world and trained with the best!
Also, you got some nerve
healing, my flunky!
Stay in your lane, dammit!
Their lives are mine!
I'm cleaning up your mess after you
let a deadly virus get out of hand!
That isn't a weapon you
should use so lightly!
I am a genius, dammit!
You think I need a raccoon
to teach me ethics? Learn!
Pleasures!
You saved me!
Get out of my way, if you want to die
so bad, then do it somewhere else!
Shut up, queen!
Our brothers were almost killed
by you, and for what? Mr.
Raccoon here saved our lives!
So tell me, what do we have to gain
for working for a maniac like you?
At least we can die for someone worth
protecting, ain't that right, guys?
Let's hear it!
Thanks, Mr. Raccoon! Mr. Raccoon!
Sir Raccoon!
No, Dr. Raccoon!
I'm forever in your debt, Mr. Raccoon! Mr.
Raccoon, that was amazing!
The Straw Hacks are lucky.
That's one good raccoon.
Go, Raccoon!
You're the best!
You can go to hell, queen!
You think I need you, chumps?
What the hell is this?
Nice work back there, raccoon.
Now do it.
You got it, Marco.
But there's one last thing I want to say.
I'll kill you, raccoon.
Rumble.
Monster point!
No!
I'm not a raccoon!
Fine!
Oops!
I'm sorry!
If we climb through the ceiling, we can
hide in the space between the floors.
I doubt anyone will look for us in there.
That's good.
Lord Momonosuke.
It's going on a little while longer.
Be brave, Momonosuke.
I know you can do this.
In truth, my heart is in turmoil.
Yamato and I have dispatched
every foe in sight.
Not because of our foes, but
because of my helplessness.
I'm a useless burden.
Enough!
You all think far too highly of me!
I have nothing! Nothing!
I am but a fool.
I am spineless and weak.
I am not worth defending.
Just let me die.
I think you're perfectly great, my lord.
There's nothing great about me.
You must give yourself time to grow.
Yes, you may be small right now, but someday
I know you'll grow into a fine shogun.
You'll be a great man someday.
You can surpass even Kozuki Oden.
You're just saying that.
It's not true.
It's not true at all!
I am a failure!
Huh?
You're an eel?
Lord Momonosuke!
I'm afraid I don't understand.
And this happens when he's troubled.
He's unable to return to his human
form until his heart is at ease.
But you weren't born this way.
Momo, did you eat a Devil Fruit?
I did.
Speaking of Kaido,
Remember when the Navy captured
him all those years ago?
Dr.
Vegapunk took the opportunity to
extract his bloodline elements,
then made an artificial
Devil Fruit from it.
Naturally, the world government
asked him to hand it over,
but in the end, his creation was
viewed as a disappointing failure.
However, they kept the fruit on Punk
Hazard instead of throwing it away.
Why are you bringing that up now?
Punk Hazard was wiped out.
It's nothing more than a memory.
I hope it was destroyed in the explosion.
But a team from Naval
Base G5 reported that one
facility on the island
was still in operation.
Well, if it was a failure, at least we know
there won't be another Kaido out there!
Who was it that patched us up?
That's still a mystery.
I thought I saw our benefactor.
But no, I must have been dreaming.
I dare say it's impossible!
While we sit here, sir, Luffy and his
friends are fighting Kaido on our behalf.
Even if we are injured, we must
return to the battle at hand.
We cannot relent until victory is ours!
Let us go!
While we still have our lives to give.
My loyal retainers!
You've had a rough run of it, haven't you?
How I've missed you all!
I see the years haven't been kind to you!
Huh?
It's...
it's Lord Odin!
It is you...
I can't blame you for being surprised.
I was sent to the future
thanks to Toki's power.
I shall explain it later.
What a tale!
My lord Odin!
It's truly a miracle!
Sorry to make you wait,
but we'll have time to celebrate
our reunion once the battle is won!
Now follow me!
We failed to slay Kaido
once, but not this time!
Of course.
We shall come with you.
I could ask for nothing more.
Let us go forth.
My Samurai, you're as loyal
as you were the day we parted!
Dammit, everyone stop!
This can't be Lord Oden.
Who are you?
Answer me!
Ashina, my friend! Kinema!
What did Lady Toki say?
We may lack the power needed
to return to the past.
However, we're able to leap ahead.
The past cannot be
altered, no matter what.
Lady Toki was only able to
send people to the future,
but she couldn't have
done that to Lord Odin.
They both died.
The history of that dark
day cannot be rewritten.
All we can do is bury our
regret and fight for tomorrow.
Just so, and we'll do it beside our Lord.
We can't.
I've had enough!
How did your senses kill him on?
Check this!
Look!
He's not even bleeding!
What? How?
Oh, Ashura.
What shameful behavior from a man who
pledged his undying loyalty to me!
What say you?
Will you be my samurai?
Watch out!
Ashura!
You've shown your true
colors, haven't you?
We all felt the same.
I wish that Lord Odin had returned to
us, but this is a snake in his guise.
What a cruel trick.
But if that's not Lord Odin,
then who are we dealing with?
He'll pay for getting my hopes up.
Ashura, are you all right?
Just hang in there.
His voice, the way he acted.
It was just like our Lord!
Only one man can mimic Lord Odin so well.
It's him!
Reveal yourself!
Kanjuro!
How could you say such a thing?
Of course I'm Odin!
You're hurt because of my mistake!
It's my fault!
I failed to finish him.
Kanjuro should be dead!
Even a sharp sword becomes
dull when pointed at a friend.
Never apologize for your kind heart.
This is nothing but a drawing.
Then where's Kanjuro?
I'm manipulating the
drawing from a distance.
Unfortunately, it's rather exhausting,
especially since I'm injured.
hear that kiku from my perspective,
your blade was pretty sharp,
in fact, i'm certain that this
battle will be my final performance!
but i have an unrelenting
force that pushes
me on my revenge towards the kozuki clan,
so i can't die just yet!
i shall pierce the heart of the.
Kozu-ki Clang, and I'll make
certain to do it with my own blade!
No!
Lord Momonosuke is in danger!
I heard a voice earlier.
An announcement I think.
It said that Lord Momonosuke
was with Haki no Ichi.
In that case, we might
be able to reach her.
All I want to do is die in peace
and you take that away from me?
You've already lost.
You'll die here unable to stop me.
And your dear Lord Odin will join you.
Don't you think he'd want
to go out with a pan?
Don't be angry.
We'll die together, like
good friends should.
I shall not know!
I shall restrain him!
Knuckles!
Save our lord and stop control!
What are you doing?
Unhand me!
Love and grief lies, I'll go!
Asuna, don't go!
You filthy rat! Let me go!
I curse you all, you bastard!
I'll never defile the name
of Kozuki Odin ever again!
You're a nut!
And now the climax, when I
shall play the lead at last.
First, I embody the Kozuki, then
I eliminate the Kozuki, and die.
An immaculate final act.
What a beautiful play my life has
been with all its twists and turns.
You bastard.
Fine then, but we're in a hurry.
You're the pain in my ass.
They sought to protect their kings.
Mere insects standing in my path.
God, I'll stay.
Everyone else keep pushing through.
Good luck.
Protect Lord Momonosuke.
Come on, King.
Let's move very well.
Please do not tarry.
Good luck.
We're all counting on you.
So the king of the day thinks
he can defeat me all on his own.
We've both been injured.
Quite the match-up.
Make no mistake.
I didn't stay behind to settle a score.
I came to put an end to this.
You, Karoo, have created enough
victims, Jack. It's over!
You have no moon to rely on.
And you have no poison.
Seems we both will have to make do.
We gotta put this fire out quick!
The water's run out!
Bring me more!
What the hell?
No, it can't be.
I'm going to relish making
you traitors pay. I was sure.
Your head came off.
You can't get back from that.
You thought you could betray me, Kaido?
Even a beheading can keep you down.
I'm sure you're not
eager for a second run.
Quite rude of Kaido, wouldn't you say?
I'll burn this castle to the ground!
When I'm done with it, Onigashima
will be nothing but a ball of fire!
There's no escape up here, and no way out!
Every last one of you will die!
That's the cost of betraying me!
Momonosuke, could you try to
change back to normal, please?
You kind of stick out.
Oh, right.
Hang in there, Lord Momonosuke. Be brave.
Sorry, I'm trying.
Despite my shameful outburst, I have
gotten better at controlling it.
When I first met Luffy and his associates,
I would transform into a dragon every
time I was surprised or became sad.
I can't help but ask, is
it like my father's power?
I wish I could turn into
a monster like he does.
At least I'd be of some use to my friends.
Luffy is still on the battlefield
fighting my father as we speak.
So what are we waiting for?
I should be fighting Kaido as Odin!
Luffy's power seems to be waning.
But for some reason, he's in
very high spirits. That's good.
Wait, I don't understand.
How can you tell?
How the hell are we supposed
to beat these two? Huh? Anyone?
Everything we do bounces
right off of them.
I guess Emperors of the Sea
are just built different.
They're trying to show off.
We can at least pretend
we've got a chance.
Just keep at it!
Our attacks have to be
doing something to them!
They're human, aren't they?
You did that earlier and it didn't work.
Think before you attack.
You say they're human.
But they're nothing like us.
That much is clear.
So what?
If you don't think you can beat
them Then why are you here?
I'm just saying we need
to come up with a good
plan first We should pull
one of them away from here
Now you're talking Those two side-by-side
are quite the gruesome spectacle
A literal vision of hell
you think this is the first
time i've been through hell
you always have that glimmer in your
eye even when the stakes are down
you're ready to die boy you first old man
You